Hi, I'm excited to work with you on using networking to find more
こんにちは 皆さんとお話しできて嬉しいです これから説明するようにネットワーキングを利用して
work opportunities.
一緒にもっとたくさんの仕事のチャンスを見つけましょう
The more people you know, or the more presence you have online,
知っている人が多いほど もしくは オンラインでのプレゼンスが増えるほど
the more likely you'll be able to find opportunities or
チャンスを見つける可能性は高くなるし チャンスの方が見つけてくれる
have opportunities find you.
かもしれません
I want to share a story with you.
まずは私の話を聞いてください
The first time I networked was when I was 13 years old.
私が初めてネットワークに触れたのは 13 才のときでした
I wanted to find an afterschool job as a babysitter.
学校の後にできるベビーシッターの 仕事を探していたんです
I asked my parents for advice.
両親にアドバイスを求めると
They told me to look at the classified ads to see who was looking.
新聞の求人広告で どういう人が募集しているのかを見なさいと言われました
To post flyers at my school to advertise.
学校でチラシを貼って 宣伝したり
And to also ask my parents' coworkers if they knew anyone looking for
両親の同僚にベビーシッターを探している人がいないか 聞いてくれるよう頼んだり
a babysitter.
しました
I actually had a few people reach out after seeing my flyers.
チラシを見た何人かの人からは実際に 連絡がありました
But I got my first biggest in gig from my friend of my mom's co-worker.
結局 最初で最大のチャンスをもらったのは 母の同僚の友人からでした
I've also used the same networking system whenever I search for a new job.
新しい仕事を探すときは いつでも同じネットワーキングシステムを使用していました
Nowadays, instead of using the classified section of the newspaper,
最近は新聞の求人欄を 見るのではなく
I search for opening on job works like Indeed and Dice.
Indeed や Dice で アルバイトを検索しています
Networking gave me access to more job works.
ネットワーキングすると よりたくさんの求人にアクセスできます
I joined a lot of local professional groups which have their own job works,
地元にあるプロフェッショナルたちのグループにも あれこれ参加しました
not open to the general public.
彼らは一般には公開していない自分の仕事を持っています
After college, I moved across the country unemployed.
大学の後 定職がないまま国中を移動して回りました
And I got a job from a posting and a local group list serve.
ポスティングとか ローカルのグループリストとかで 仕事を見つけました
For most of my career, I would say my LinkedIn profile was pretty bad,
キャリアのほとんどの期間 私の LinkedIn プロファイルはひどかったと思います
because I didn't take it seriously.
真面目に考えてなかったから
However, one day, I took the advice from Udacity's LinkedIn course, and
でもある日 Udacity の LinkedIn コースで アドバイスをもらって
rebranded myself on my page.
マイページで自分をリブランドしたんです
I got three emails from recruiters that week.
その週のうちにリクルーターから 3 通も メールが届きました
Those recruiters found me because I optimized my LinkedIn profile for
リクルーターが私を見つけてくれたのは 自分の LinkedIn プロファイルを検索用に
searches.
最適化したからです
And instead of asking my parents coworkers for
両親の同僚のつてをたどるんじゃなくて オフ会や合コンに参加して
job leads, I attended meetups and mixers to connect with people in the industry.
業界の人たちと つながるようにしました
And I have found job opportunities that way.
こういう方法で 私は仕事の チャンスを掴みました
I found my current job at Udacity through a conversation with someone
Udacity の今の仕事は テクノロジー業界の人との会話からです
in the tech industry who I actually didn’t know all that well at the time.
そのときはあまりよく 知らない人でした
You don't know where opportunity will come from.
チャンスはどこにあるか わかりません
And the best way to make sure you don't miss out on opening,
仕事の空きがあってそれを見過ごして しまわないようにする一番の方法は
is to have a great online presence and network.
オンラインプレゼンスとネットワークを 大きくすること
In this lesson, we'll review how to network and
このレッスンでは ネットワークの方法をおさらいして
spend some time on personal branding,
個人のブランディングについても少し触れて
which will make sure your networking attempts lead to job opportunities.
皆さんのネットワーキングが確実に 仕事につながるようにしましょう